<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
    <article no="05082021">
        <title>Life never goes as planned</title>
        <date>May 08, 2021</date>
        <text>
            <indent semantic="p">
                I have been on the border trails, around Mount Gosford, which I found on AllTrails. I had never been to hike in Maine or near this mountain range. 
                It's nice because you can make a loop from where you park your car, without needing a reservation. I thought this hike would be easy to do: the map on 
                AllTrails said about 25km which is perfect for a long day of hiking, but I found the elevation gain to be really, really high and the trails were a lot longer 
                than expected, 10km longer. I think the maps weren't accurate for all of the switchbacks on this trail given the lack of detail. However, it was a beautiful 
                trip with lots of wildlife and views. There is a small cliff called Cap-Frontière where there is a magnificent view of Maine with mountains, lakes and flowers 
                as far as the eye can see. The unexpected nature of this hike, i.e. the terrain and the mapping, made it a little more difficult than expected and disappointing 
                for myself as my organization and planning was not so good in the end. Then, I remembered a book by my favorite French author and explorer, Sylvain Tesson, 
                on the importance of “s'abandonner à vivre”.
            </indent> 
            <indent semantic="q">
                Il est rare en voyage de vivre des jours conformes aux idées que l’on s’étaient forgées avant les grands départs. D'habitude, voyager c'est faire voir du pays 
                à sa déception.
            </indent>
            <indent semantic="p">
                And that's life. Things hardly ever go according to plan whether traveling or in everyday life, and I think we have to accept that by changing our outlook on 
                the course of things. Maybe we have impossible standards or are we looking for answers to unsolvable problems? In fact, the world has always been like this and 
                always will be. Let's avoid disappointment. Therefore, I am convinced that there is an alternative in being open to everything around us, and welcoming them 
                as they come. But, it does require space in our mind, because the more we restrict ourselves in expectations and rules, the less flexibility and openness we end 
                up having towards the messiness of life. Each new experience is an opportunity to discover something new about yourself or the world. It is only by breaking habits 
                and opening up to the unexpected in each of our decisions and actions that life can offer its full potential.
            </indent>
        </text>
    </article>
</articles>
