<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
    <article no="08052021">
        <title>Life never goes as planned. And that's ok</title>
        <date>May 08, 2021</date>
        <metadata>
            <localisation>Stoke Mountains</localisation>
            <length>18,97 km</length>
            <elevation>890 m</elevation>
            <climax>653 m</climax>
            <viewpoint>180&#176;</viewpoint>
            <duration>6.30</duration>
        </metadata>
        <text>
            <paragraph>One nice spring Saturday, I had everything organized for a hike on the border trails towards Mount Saddle. I had planned all the tough climbs and vantage points, and read all the trail maps to optimize my day and my training. I wanted to cover a long distance for a day hike, 25km so I couldn't do this without a good plan. So everything had to be fine, or should have.</paragraph>
            <paragraph>After a few hours of walking, I finally start to gain altitude and reach a point of view. However, what I see does not correspond to my research on the route. I wonder without worrying yet, and luckily, crosses paths with two hunters. One of them asks me where I'm going like this, to which I answer: Mount Saddle. Their eyes meet before pointing me away:- Mount Saddle is the little blue spot that you can see on the horizon. It's a very long distance, I hope you know what you're getting into!- I thank him with a nervous little laugh, and continue my journey (ah, damn attitude of never giving up).</paragraph>
            <paragraph>So let's do the topo. At the start of the trail I took the wrong section only to realize far too late that I had embarked on a detour of an additional 10 km. On a very hot and sunny day, and given the level of difficulty of the trail, I was starting to worry a bit about the risk of dehydration.</paragraph>
            <paragraph>At the time, I was really disappointed with myself and felt bitterness, because I really wanted this day as I had planned it. And that's when I remembered a quote from one of my favorite author-explorers: `` It is rare on a trip to live days in accordance with the ideas that we had forged before the great departures. ''</paragraph>
        </text>
        <multimedia>
            <image status="1"/>
            <image status="2"/>
            <image status="3"/>
            <image status="4"/>
            <image status="5"/>
            <image status="6"/>
            <image status="7"/>
            <image status="8"/>
        </multimedia>
    </article>
</articles>
